[
   {
      "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I need to concentrate ___ my homework.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) of",
          "rightOption": "b"
         }
   },
   {
      "question":
        {
          "prompt": "He's really bad ___ cooking.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) for",
          "optionC": "c) with",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
      "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I've always had difficulty ___ math.",
          "optionA": "a) against",
          "optionB": "b) from",
          "optionC": "c) with",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "Mark applied ___ a scholarship.",
          "optionA": "a) for",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) to",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I'm incapable ___ playing sports.",
          "optionA": "a) to",
          "optionB": "b) about",
          "optionC": "c) of",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
          "question":
        {
          "prompt": "They have to work ___ this project.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) with",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I need a moment to recover ___ the shock.",
          "optionA": "a) from",
          "optionB": "b) about",
          "optionC": "c) against",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "These sneakers are not suitable ___ jogging.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) for",
          "optionC": "c) of",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
           "question":
        {
          "prompt": "This book had a profound influence ___ me.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) for",
          "optionC": "c) on",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I've always struggled ___ Physics at school.",
          "optionA": "a) with",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) about",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "She asked ___ the condition of the house.",
          "optionA": "a) about",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) in",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I'm certain ___ it.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) about",
          "optionC": "c) in",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "The hotel has the advantage ___ being cheap.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) of",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "This town is specialized ___ receiving tourists.",
          "optionA": "a) in",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) about",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
         "question":
        {
          "prompt": "The event was crowded ___ young people.",
          "optionA": "a) in",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) with",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
           "question":
        {
          "prompt": "They deserve the credit ___ planning the trip.",
          "optionA": "a) with",
          "optionB": "b) for",
          "optionC": "c) of",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
           "question":
        {
          "prompt": "She just glanced ___ the newspaper.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) of",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
           "question":
        {
          "prompt": "We were furious ___ the hotel manager.",
          "optionA": "a) with",
          "optionB": "b) against",
          "optionC": "c) about",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
           "question":
        {
          "prompt": "Everyone was surprised ___ the low prices.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) in",
          "optionC": "c) of",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
           "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I trust ___ your ability.",
          "optionA": "a) at",
          "optionB": "b) on",
          "optionC": "c) in",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   }
]
